

I'm a passionate web and app developer with expertise in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. My journey began with programming at a young age, and I have continued to refine my skills through various self-taught projects and professional experience



+33 7 45 05 36 75



51 Rue de la Chartreuse



youneslahouiti@duck.com



https://younes-portfoliodev.vercel.app/

Younes Lahouiti

Fullstack developer

Skills

- Front-end Development
- Back-end Development
- Database Management
- API Integration
- Deployment and Maintenance
- Testing and Debugging

Experience

2017-2020: Highschool

 Developed small Python apps for solving 1st and 2nd degree equations

2020-2021: College

 Attended college for Computer Science, but chose to discontinue

2021-2023: OpenClassrooms

 Successfully completed the Web Development and Front-End Development programs from OpenClassrooms, earning two diplomas

Education History

2020-2021

Université Claude Bernard Lyon 1

• Computer Science

2021-2023

OpenClassrooms

- Diploma in Web development
- Diploma in Front-End development